wesprodigital.com 2015-05-23

# Privacy Policy | www.wesprodigital.com

WesproDigital.com is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Privacy of customer is important to us. We collect all your privacy information where it is necessary for us. This privacy policy governs the product and services to better serve you and make you clearly understand your information at our site. When you use the site, you cons tent to our collection, use and disclosure of information about you as described in this privacy policy. Please read the following information carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

**Information we use**  
WesproDigital.com collects information when you use our site. We believe in that our customer or visitors should have knowledge that what type of information we collect, the information includes Email, Name, Company Name, Street Address, Post Code, City, Country, Gender, Telephone Number, Delivery address, Password, Payment Details, payment card details or bank account details.  
We may use the information for purposes such as to provide site functionality, order processing, Claims, order tracking, provide feedback to business & Professionals whose products & Services are listed on site, provide customer support; evaluate the success of our advertising, fulfill transactions authorized by you on our site and comply with legal obligations.

**Information Sharing**  
We May offer sign on services that enable you to access the website with your login credentials. We do not rent or sell your personal contact information with the third parties to use for their own marketing purposes.  Your personal contact information may share with our agents and contractors to carry out the performance and functionality of the site, or fulfill your requests, provide customer support.  
**Security**  
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure – so we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
Protection of your personal data  
We protect your information by using technical and administrative security measures that limit the risk of loss, abuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, and alteration. Nevertheless, if you believe your account has been abused, please contact us through email us on support@wesprodigital.com

**Marketing Purposes**  
You agree that we may use the information collected by us to send you offers, whether personalized or not, or to contact you by telephone regarding products or services offered by wesprodigital.com. We may combine your information with the information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services & Functionalities.
